{
    "id": "fdb2d803c4ef49eeb607452a1ee12ee4",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He does not smoke, …………………………. does he drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1fde5ff43aa144569ae347b1aee17c68"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must apologize, ………………………. you will be punished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d592dcdccee24c519b6d4e9653be8496"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be asleep, ………………………….. there is no light in his room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "922bc73af83b44e686ac4d6af2f4784b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been working hard, ………………………… he will pass.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8150d6fc5b644b4a8f86ed24becb5256"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will promote him …………………………… he is efficient.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94269fe7532747e8b4cdef959da6d2de"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t help you, ………………………… you tell me the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a295a506446443891d6a2a24e909a2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks ……………………………. it might rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "if",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33df8b88b2044d3d947c16d705259a1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. she is poor, she is always neatly dressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d92e17bed61448dcb44a20f750176d48"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have such regard for him ……………………………… I will do anything to please him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23cb327ae02640128d67d3a42e4b13c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He climbed up a tree ……………………………… to get a good view of the procession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such as",
                "so as",
                "such that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "328588d465c44a719a43e3c7df10766d"
        }
    ]
}